He's her biggest blind spot.
Eenie Meanie is a thriller, action, comedy film directed by Shawn Simmons.
A former teenage getaway driver gets dragged back into her unsavory past when a former employer
offers her a chance to save the life of her chronically unreliable ex-boyfriend.
Edie, played by Samara Weaving.
John, played by Karl Glusman.
Nico, played by Andy Garcia.
Dad Meaney, played by Steve Zahn.
The Chaperone, played by Jermaine Fowler.
Perm Walters, played by Marshawn Lynch.
Eenie Meanie is a 2025 American heist comedy thriller film written and
directed by Shawn Simmons, in his feature directorial debut.
Samara Weaving leads an ensemble cast that includes Karl Glusman,
Jermaine Fowler, Marshawn Lynch, Steve Zahn, and Andy Garcia.
It was released on Hulu on August 22, 2025.
The tone is lighthearted and intense.